Who's in charge here?
Where is the air support?
So...
Gerard...
I suspect you have a good reason
for pulling me away from my ...duties.
Your vodka can wait, my good Alexi.
Come, stand here. You need to see this.
I know all about the Zerg, Gerard.
We've all seen the tapes a hundred...
You've seen nothing!
Dissecting a dead Zerg
in a lab is one thing
unleashing them on man is another.
You must go into this with both eyes open.
Once started, there's no going back.
Are you prepared
to go all the way with this, Alexi?
Yes.
Yes, I am prepared
to go all the way, my good admiral.
Good. Good, I knew I could count on you.
Admiral. The colonist's base
will be overrun in a matter of minutes.
Shall we intervene?
Take us into orbit, Mr. Malmsteen.
We've seen enough.