I can’t see a thing, Jim.
Well hold on.
I swear, it’s always some damn thing.
Wait, got it.
Aw hell, this thing ain’t gonna hold.
Shut up.
Damn you’re ugly.
You girls strapped in nice and tight now?
Tighter than your momma’s...
That’s a good one man.
Locked in and cruising.
What you got for me out there, Joey Ray?
We got Terran for sure.
I don’t know about the rest.
We got a big ol’ buttload
of floating debris out here.
We hittin’ pay dirt this time for sure.
Explain to me
how we gonna get all this home?
I’m detached and moving toward
the derelict spacecraft.
Damn it Jim, video’s out again.
Well quit picking at it.
I ain’t pickin’ at it, damn it!
I’m out here with a hitch in my giddy up
and you’re in there….. (mumbles)
(Spanish) Hey, can you hear me?
(Spanish) They're always talking
when they don't have the...
(Spanish) ...leaving me hanging out
here in space doing nothing...
(Spanish) Can you hear me?
Hey, you listening to me?
Hold on. I've got visual.
It’s a damn bogie, 12 o’clock!
(Spanish) Oh my God, save me Jesus Christ!
Up behind the ship! Look behind you Jim!
(Spanish) Mother of God, no!