Fellow Terrans,
I come to you in the wake
of recent events
to issue a call to reason.
Let no human deny the perils of our time.
While we battle one another
divided by the petty strife
of our common history
the tide of greater conflict
is turning against us
threatening to destroy all
that we have accomplished.
It is time for us, as nations
and as individuals
to set aside our long-standing feuds
and unite.
The tides of an unwinnable war
are upon us.
And we must seek refuge upon higher ground
lest we be swept away by the flood.
The Confederacy is no more.
Whatever semblance of unity
and protection it once provided
is a phantom, a memory.
With our enemies left unchecked
who will you turn to for protection?
The devastation wrought
by the alien invaders is self-evident.
We have seen
our homes and communities destroyed
by the calculated blows of the Protoss.
We have seen first-hand
our friends and loved ones
consumed by the nightmarish Zerg.
Unprecedented and unimaginable
though they may be
these are the signs of our time.
The time has come, my fellow Terrans
to rally to a new banner.
In unity lies strength.
Already, many of the dissident factions
have joined us.
Out of the many we shall forge
an indivisible whole
capitulating only to a single throne
and from that throne
I shall watch over you.
From this day forward
let no human make war
upon any other human.
Let no Terran agency
conspire against this new beginning
and let no man consort with alien powers
and to all the enemies of Humanity
seek not to bar our way.
For we shall win through
no matter the cost!