The very mention
of this terrifying race
once brought fear to all who heard it.
But now we can all rest easy
as our own forces now occupy
their very homeworld of Char.
Months have passed since
our initial confrontation with the Zerg
and now Directorate forces
have taken control of the planet Char
long since rumored to cradle
the malevolent Overmind of the Zerg.
The Overmind itself
an enormous living brain-like entity
dictates control
of all the myriad Zerg forces
and it was believed
to be planning
an invasion of the Earth itself!
Once on the offensive
our highly-trained Directorate forces
were more than a match
for the beast-like Zerg.
Even their fiercest warrior breed
could not defeat
the greatest
military technology in the galaxy.
The Zerg forces on Char
were completely decimated
and their losses
were tallied in the millions.
But all wars have casualties
and while Directorate losses were minimal
the fleet's Vice-Admiral Stukov
gave his life during
the final valiant assault on Char.
Memorial services were held
aboard the Directorate flaship,
Aleksander.
Vice-Admiral Stukov truly knew
the meaning of sacrifice.
Yet his sacrifice was not in vain.
The Overmind itself
was the prize of the battle.
Even now, Directorate psychics
and powerful drugs
are keeping the creature pacified.
The Overmind will undergo
extensive research
to ensure the continued safety
of the United Earth Directorate
and of all mankind.