Once again, I stand atop
the broken bodies of my enemies
victorious, but not unscarred.
The Earth-born Directorate
has been destroyed
and the Overmind lies dead and trampled
beneath the ashes of Char.
As for my unlikely allies
I think that I shall allow them a reprieve
for in time I will seek to test
their resolve and their strengths.
They will all be mine in the end
for I am the Queen of Blades.
None shall ever dispute my rule… again.
Dearest Helena
by now the news of our defeat
has reached the Earth.
The creatures we were sent here
to tame are untamable…
And the colonies we were sent to reclaim
have proven to be stronger
than we anticipated.
Whatever you may hear
about what has happened out here
know this: Alexi
did not die gloriously in battle.
I killed him...
my pride killed him.
And now my pride has consumed me as well.
You will never see me again, Helena.
Tell our children that I love them
and that their father died
in defense of their future.
Au revoir.